Shahanshah Alam

Sr. Software Engineer

A dynamic professional with 3.5+ years of experience seeking opportunity to apply extensive expertise of Software developer skills in an increasingly responsible manner. A proactive person who has the ability to unlearn and relearn what is required to reach organizational goal.

alamshanu875@gmail.com

+91 9646352514

Noida, India

linkedin.com/in/shahanshah-alam-05a455134

stackoverflow.com/users/10407485/shan-alam? tab=profile



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Software Engineer

Cutshort

10/2022 - Present

Responsibility

- Leading react native team.
- · Creating Cutshort app with team of 4 members.

Software Engineer

Appventurez Mobitech Pvt Ltd &

01/2020 - 09/2022

Responsibility

- Worked as Software engineer and have worked on 6 apps.
- · Worked on projects from scratch to deployment.
- Built various functionality eg. chat, social media integration, multimedia etc.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology

Chandigarh Engineering College

07/2016 - 06/2020 Courses

Information Technology

SKILLS

React Native

JavaScript

TypeScript

PROJECTS (8)

Cutshort

- Cutshort is a modern Al-based job search app to find your next job effortlessly at top companies & startups in India.
- Android
- ios

Nar'aakom

- Nar'aakom app allows people in Qatar to benefit from many of PHCC's digital services from their smartphones.
- Android
- ios

Bando

- Bando is the mobile application built by Artists for Artists to monitor and monetise their most loyal fans' engagement in one place.
- Android
- <u>iOS</u>

Khadi India

- E-Commerce app where khadi and village industries can sell their products.
- Android
- iOS

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

• • •

• • •

INTERESTS

Cricket